<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>adamspe.github.io</title>
    <description>Notio Software LLC is my small (small as in me) software consulting company.  Some of my projects, mostly learning/examples, I&#39;m hosting in the github repos.  It&#39;s an amazing tool/community for sharing open source software and knowledge in general.
</description>
    <link>http://adamspe.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://adamspe.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 09:31:55 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 09:31:55 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>D3 Force Layout</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For an upcoming project I will be working on (via &lt;a href=&quot;http://djcase.com&quot;&gt;DJCase&lt;/a&gt; for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.usanpn.org&quot;&gt;USA National Phenology Network&lt;/a&gt;) there will be a heavy visualization component.  I’m hooked on, and am hoping to make use of, &lt;a href=&quot;http://d3js.org&quot;&gt;D3&lt;/a&gt; for all the visualizations.  While putting together the proposal to try to land the work I wrote several bar graphs and bubbly sorts of charts but some of it remained (and remains) greek to me.  So in an effort to get my head more completely wrapped
around joins, layouts, etc. I dug around for some potentially interesting data (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.census.gov/compendia/statab/cats/prices/consumer_price_indexes_cost_of_living_index.html&quot;&gt;Consumer Price Indexes, Cost of Living Index from the most recent census&lt;/a&gt;) and dreamed up a, perhaps not practical, way of visualizing that information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to post-process what I learned (and clean up the code) so hopefully I’ll write more about it later but for now &lt;a href=&quot;http://adamspe.github.io/d3_census/&quot;&gt;here’s a link to what came out the other side&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://adamspe.github.io/d3/angularjs/2014/11/19/d3-force.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://adamspe.github.io/d3/angularjs/2014/11/19/d3-force.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>d3</category>
        
        <category>angularjs</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
